nailthedeal.com 2016-10-26

# Privacy statement|Dubai GroupBuy|Nail the Deal - Nail the Deal |DubaiVoucher|Dubai Discount

Nail The Deal the provider of the Website (referred to as "us" or "we"), is firmly committed to protecting the privacy of our users. Our goal is to provide you with a secure online experience and to ensure that any information you submit to us is private and used/disclosed only for the purposes and in the means described below. This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the Nail The Deal websites (collectively, the "Website"). Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (the "User" or the "End User") and how we use that information.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE. 

**1\. Changes to Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**2\. Types of Information Collected and Uses of Collected Information**

We collect two types of information about our Website Users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Personally Identifiable Information - Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies a specific End User. When you engage in certain activities on the Website, such as creating an account, filling out a survey, posting a review, sending us feedback, requesting information about our services, or applying for a job through the Website (collectively, "Identification Activities"), we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. It is optional for you to engage in an Identification Activity. If you elect to engage in an Identification Activity, however, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information about yourself, such as your first and last name, mailing address, email address, and telephone number. Depending on the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some is identified as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information for a particular activity that requires it, you will not be permitted to engage in that activity.

**3\. All credit/debit cards details or information will NOT be stored, sold, shared, rented or leased to any third parties.**

**Refer-A-Friend / Buy it for a Friend -** If you choose to use our referral service or buy a deal for a friend, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email with the gift you bought for them or inviting him or her to visit the site. Nail The Deal stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email, sending their gift, and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [support@nailthedeal.com](mailto:support@nailthedeal.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

We use Personally Identifiable Information to provide products and services to you, enhance the operation of the Website, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze Website use, improve our product and service offerings, and to tailor your experience with third parties as provided in Item 3 of this Privacy Policy. For example, if you send our customer service an email we may use your comments and feedback to tell others about our services, and may post your comment in our marketing materials or on our Website. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to trouble.

**4\. Unsubscribe**

To Unsubscribe, you can simply use our 1 touch unsubscribe button which is present on all our emailers at the bottom.

**5\. Cookies**

Nail the Deal uses technologies such as cookies and pixels to keep track of your activities on our website and our Advertiser's websites, and to serve you more relevant advertisements. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your device for record-keeping purposes. Session cookies expire when you close your browser. Persistent cookies remain on your device for an extended period of time. We and our third party partners use session cookies and persistent cookies to make it easier for you to navigate and enhance the experience of our site, and to monitor and evaluate our website's operation and use.

We use persistent cookies to keep track of your activities when you visit our website or our Advertisers' websites, and to serve you relevant advertisements. Our Advertising Partners also place persistent cookies on your device when you visit our website or our Advertisers' websites in order to help us recognize you and serve relevant advertisements to you when you visit their website or online service or websites in their networks. AdRoll's policy is that our Advertising Partners only collect information that does not personally or directly identify you via these cookies and we will cease working with partners found violating this policy. You can remove cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. You may also decline our cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website.

**Nail the Deal (Subsidiary of Cosmos Star Consultants)**  
Office 1412 Grosvenor Business Tower   
TECOM, Sheikh Zayad Road  
P.O.Box 31705,   
Dubai, United Arab Emirates

**Customer Support :**
